I
나
Care deeply about quality of life
삶의 질에 대한 깊은 관심
One hundred yuan
100위안
Think of it as making yourself happy
스스로를 행복하게 만드는 일이라고 생각하세요
Although it's easy
쉽지만
very comfortable
아주 편안한
But the sound is not good at all
하지만 소리는 전혀 좋지 않습니다
Just throwing garbage in my ear
그냥 귀에 쓰레기를 던지는 것 뿐이야
In any case
어쨌든
I can't accept it
나는 그것을 받아들일 수 없다
this
이것
I have a picture
사진이 있어요
Let's go there and take a look
거기로 가서 살펴보자
Let's go
갑시다
Thanks
감사해요
Good
좋은
Welcome
환영
Do you have an umbrella?
우산 있어요?
The umbrella has been sold
우산이 팔렸습니다
You can come in and take a look
들어오셔서 구경하시면 됩니다
This song is really suitable for listening on a rainy day
비 오는 날 듣기에 정말 어울리는 노래입니다
are you strong?
너 힘 세니?
My car
내 차
It looks like the electric bottle ran out of battery
전기병 배터리가 다 된 것 같아요
Can you help me drive it to the car repair plant
자동차 수리 공장까지 운전하는 것을 도와주실 수 있나요?
The rain stopped
비가 멈췄다
Thanks
감사해요
truly
진심으로
Help me
도와주세요
Have you ever sat down?
혹시 자리에 앉아본 적 있나요?
No no
아니 아니
Do you dare to sit down?
감히 앉으실 수 있나요?
I dare
감히
Good
좋은
I will contact you after fixing it
수정 후 연락드리겠습니다
Mr. Chen
첸 씨
The technology section has been completed
기술 부문이 완료되었습니다.
Security check
보안 검색
For safe checking
안전한 점검을 위해
Temporarily not found
일시적으로 찾을 수 없음
Any theft equipment
도난 장비
who participated in the competition
대회에 참가한 사람
I checked it
확인했어요
There is nothing abnormal
이상한 건 하나도 없어
If the night fog
밤 안개가 끼면
In competition
경쟁 중
It will definitely start
분명 시작될 거야
Special attention should be paid
특별한 주의를 기울여야 한다
Such as Shi Li and Yu Xiaoyue
Shi Li와 Yu Xiaoyue와 같은
Such as Shi Liyu and Xiao Yue
Shi Liyu 및 Xiao Yue와 같은
Understood
이해했다
We have increased background investigation
배경 조사를 늘렸습니다.
Check in on employees in the competition
경쟁에 참여하는 직원을 확인하세요
Did you participate in the special game?
스페셜 게임에 참여하셨나요?
Now the spy method
이제 스파이 방법
more and more
점점 더
It gets very difficult
매우 어려워진다
In our work
우리 일에서는
Special game
특별한 게임
Although the meeting
비록 회의는
From the real world
현실 세계에서
To virtual space
가상공간으로
But in the end
하지만 결국
They must complete
완료해야 합니다.
In real time
실시간
Understood
이해했다
become
~이 되다
I didn't find this
나는 이것을 찾지 못했습니다.
The video in which Xiao Yi is invited to participate
샤오이가 참여하도록 초대받은 영상
There is no at all
전혀 없습니다
no
아니요
Was he really a professional driver?
그는 정말 전문 운전자였나요?
Well understood
잘 이해했습니다
Hey beautiful
헤이 아름다운
Has your car been modified?
당신의 자동차는 개조되었나요?
Good
좋은
Well done, sister
잘했어요 언니
You can train for three months
3개월 동안 훈련할 수 있어요
You can participate in the external match
외부 경기에 참가할 수 있습니다.
No need, no need
필요없어, 필요없어
I'm just playing
난 그냥 놀고 있어요
I do not intend to participate in the competition
나는 대회에 참가할 생각이 없다
in my opinion
내 생각에는
You have to play at a higher level
더 높은 레벨에서 플레이해야 합니다.
thus
따라서
I will find a coach for you later
나중에 코치를 찾아줄게
You can improve it
개선할 수 있습니다.
Okay I'll think
알았어 생각해 볼게
Good
좋은
Trainer Xiao Yi's bike
트레이너 샤오이의 자전거
Was it edited by itself?
직접 편집한 걸까요?
Yes
예
Has its own design workshop
자체 디자인 워크샵을 보유하고 있습니다.
Is he in that section?
그 사람이 그 구역에 있나요?
Yes, this door
응, 이 문
I'm not working overtime today
나 오늘 초과근무 안 해
I'll pick you up in a moment
잠시 후에 데리러 갈게요
I'll see you later
나중에 봐요
Something to do
할 일
I have a remote control lock
리모컨 잠금장치가 있어요
Is there a way to open it?
열 수 있는 방법이 있나요?
Leave it to me
나에게 맡겨
Good
좋은
What do you want to eat tonight?
오늘 밤에는 무엇을 먹고 싶나요?
I don't know
모르겠습니다
I know there is a hot pot chow shan restaurant
훠궈 차우샨 레스토랑이 있는 걸 알아요
Very delicious
아주 맛있는
You can try
당신은 시도 할 수 있습니다
Chu Yan
추얀
Are you with us tonight?
오늘 밤 우리와 함께 계시나요?
No opinion was provided
의견이 제공되지 않았습니다.
Chu Yan
추얀
I did not expect
나는 기대하지 않았다
you have a lover
당신은 애인이 있어요
I will go
나는 갈 것이다
I did not expect
나는 기대하지 않았다
Yes, her boyfriend is very handsome
응, 그 남자친구 정말 잘생겼어
Do you need this light?
이 조명이 필요해요?
Okay
좋아요
dear
~에게
Did you hear this?
이 말을 들었나요?
where are we going?
우리 어디로 가는 거야?
You'll know when we're gone
우리가 가면 넌 알게 될 거야
Let's go
갑시다
Is there such a good place in Tianhai?
텐하이에 이런 좋은 곳이 있나요?
I can't find anyone local
현지인을 찾을 수 없어요
How did you find it?
어떻게 찾았나요?
After a while taste their seafood
잠시 후 해산물을 맛보세요
better
더 나은
am I
나는인가?
He's been ignoring you lately
그 사람이 최근에 당신을 무시하고 있어요
Our project
우리의 계획
To a new stage
새로운 무대로
There is a new order in the company
회사에 새로운 주문이 왔습니다
You are not allowed to bring your phone to work
직장에 휴대폰을 가져갈 수 없습니다.
But I promise you
하지만 약속할게
after finishing the work
일을 마친 후
I will never ignore you
나는 결코 당신을 무시하지 않을 것입니다
Lots of clouds today
오늘은 구름이 많아
I don't know soon
곧 모르겠어
Can you see the sunset?
일몰을 볼 수 있나요?
Why didn't you wear glasses today?
오늘 왜 안경을 안 썼어요?
I changed the hidden glasses
숨겨진 안경을 바꿨어요
Why
왜
Isn't this beautiful?
정말 아름답지 않나요?
Wear nice glasses
안경 잘 쓰세요
Do you comfort me?
나를 위로해 주나요?
I have lived well since I was young
나는 어렸을 때부터 잘 살았다.
I am a transparent, unimpressive person
나는 투명하고 인상이 없는 사람이다
But you are different
하지만 당신은 달라요
You live a free life
당신은 자유로운 삶을 살고 있습니다
So handsome
너무 잘생겼어
He is a brilliant person
그는 훌륭한 사람이다
When others see us
다른 사람들이 우리를 볼 때
He will feel inappropriate
그는 부적절하다고 느낄 것이다
Originally I think
원래 내 생각에는
We are not from the same world
우리는 같은 세계 출신이 아니다
but I wish
하지만 나는 바란다
Come here
이리 오세요
This is good
이것은 좋다
Do you want to do something bad?
뭔가 나쁜 짓을 하고 싶나요?
not good
안좋다
Good
좋은
To where
어디로
Let's go
갑시다
Is this possible?
이것이 가능한가?
Get on the boat Get on the boat
배에 타라 배에 타라
Will he be arrested?
그는 체포될 것인가?
Sit down
앉아
Are you sure you can?
정말로 할 수 있나요?
Chu Yan Chu Yan
추얀 추얀
You can drive
넌 운전할 수있어
I cannot
나는 할 수 없다
I am driving
나는 운전 중입니다
there
거기
this
이것
No, it's too fast
아니요, 너무 빠릅니다
Something, open the door
뭐야, 문 좀 열어봐
do you know
당신은 알고 있나요
sunset
일몰
Was the sun up eight minutes ago?
8분 전에 해가 떴나요?
Yes
예
before one hour
한 시간 전에
Do you know except the sun
태양 빼고는 아시나요?
The stars closest to us
우리에게 가장 가까운 별
From the half horse tower?
반마탑에서요?
stars
별
What is stars?
별이란 무엇입니까?
The sun is the stars
태양은 별이다
The sun is the sun
태양은 태양이다
The sun is not the stars
태양은 별이 아니다
You know astronomy
당신은 천문학을 알고
Astronomy is interesting
천문학은 흥미롭다
Occasionally
가끔
It will give us more recognition
그러면 우리가 더 많은 인정을 받을 것입니다.
And look
그리고 봐
For example
예를 들어
Do you know the star of Newlang
뉴랑의 별을 아시나요?
And star
그리고 별
I know
알아요
Do you know how far it is?
얼마나 먼지 아시나요?
almost
거의
Twenty cm
20cm
14.5 light years
14.5광년
How far is it?
얼마나 머니?
If sent
전송된 경우
From Niolang star
니오랑스타에서
Detection device for five thousand meters
5,000미터 감지 장치
You need approx
대략 필요합니다
Three million years
삼백만년
Can't you drive fast?
빨리 운전할 수 없나요?
Go
가다
But you know that three million years
하지만 당신은 300만 년이라는 것을 알고 있습니다.
in the universe
우주에서
Do you feel I'm boring?
내가 지루하다고 느끼나요?
I think you are interesting
내 생각엔 당신이 흥미로운 것 같아요
fun
재미있는
Know astronomy
천문학을 알다
Know the sun and the star
태양과 별을 알아라
Niu Lang and Cheng
니우 랑과 쳉
That is, a year of light
즉, 빛의 해
She knows a lot of the language
그녀는 그 언어를 많이 알고 있다
He translated a lot
그 사람 번역 많이 했어
Things I don't understand
내가 이해하지 못하는 것들
I'm starting to like you
나는 당신을 좋아하기 시작했다
You're comforting me again
또 나를 위로하는구나
I'll tell you a secret
비밀 하나 알려줄게
In reality
실제로는
I do not believe
난 믿지 않아
I do not believe that
믿을 수 없어
Do you hate me?
당신은 날 싫어합니까?
no
아니요
Goodbye, priest
안녕히 계십시오, 신부님
Don't make me wait for you for three million years
내가 당신을 300만년 동안 기다리게 만들지 마세요
I will go
나는 갈 것이다
Good night, good night
잘 자요, 잘 자요
Take care, Niu Lang
조심해, 니우 랑
This is amazing
이거 엄청나 네
Xiao Yi
샤오이
Length and shape
길이와 모양
Including car riding mode
자동차 라이딩 모드 포함
Looks like a suspect
피의자 같은데
Their position is similar
둘의 입장은 비슷하다
Yes
예
If a person wants to change intentionally
사람이 의도적으로 변화를 원하는 경우
Its own habit movement
나만의 습관운동
very Difficult
매우 어렵다
Especially the car riding position
특히 차를 타는 자세
Are there any other doubts?
다른 의심은 없나요?
this person
이 사람
It has its own space for change
변화를 위한 고유한 공간이 있습니다.
Next to the car
차 옆
It is very hidden
아주 숨겨져 있어요
And I'm inside
그리고 나는 안에 있어요
I found a car from the Kakuka Ninja
카쿠카 닌자에게서 차를 찾았어요
The engine has been modified
엔진이 수정되었습니다
Horse power is strong enough
말의 힘은 충분히 강하다
And this car
그리고 이 차
I recently moved out
최근에 이사했어요
There is a mark on a sticker on the car
자동차 스티커에 표시가 있습니다.
There is no license plate
번호판이 없습니다
Even if I use it sometimes
가끔 사용해도
It will not take off the car plate
그것은 차 판을 벗지 않을 것입니다
So suspect
그러니까 의심해
very big
매우 크다
Today I want
오늘 나는 원한다
To go take a video of his car ride
그의 차를 타는 모습을 동영상으로 찍으러 가세요
But he found out
그러나 그는 알아냈다
He came to talk to me
그 사람이 나한테 얘기하러 왔어
Just a spy
그냥 스파이
He has high alertness
그는 경계심이 높다
We can keep an eye on him
우리는 그를 계속 지켜볼 수 있어요
maybe
아마도
But you must be very careful
하지만 정말 조심해야 해요
Go remove your makeup
가서 화장을 지우고
This is the technology department
기술부입니다
Let me introduce you
소개할게요
New colleague Huang Zicheng
새로운 동료 황쯔쳉
He is also a new system administrator
그는 또한 새로운 시스템 관리자이기도 합니다.
New system administrator
새로운 시스템 관리자
Come sit here
여기로 와서 앉으세요
Who ordered milk tea?
누가 밀크티를 주문했나요?
here here
여기 여기
This tea
이 차
The afternoon tea I requested for everyone
모두에게 부탁한 애프터눈 티
In the future
미래에
please
제발
Thanks
감사해요
thank you thank you
감사합니다 감사합니다
.Let's go
.갑시다
“Xiang
“샹
.Come here
.이리 오세요
Come on this
어서 이
No, there is no need for that
아니요, 그럴 필요는 없습니다.
“Xiang
“샹
.I'll find out later
.나중에 알아보겠습니다
Work process
작업 과정
Communicate
의사소통하다
Welcome
환영
I want to ask
나는 묻고 싶다
what is there
어떤이
What is the content of the work?
작품의 내용은 무엇인가요?
Secure check
보안검사
Improve sex check loopholes
성별 확인 허점 개선
Is she strong at work?
그녀는 직장에서 강한가요?
decent
품위 있는
Are you good at the program or the program
프로그램을 잘하는가, 프로그램을 잘하는가?
They are all good
그들은 모두 좋다
So if nothing else
그러니 다른 게 없다면
I'm going to work
나는 일하러 갈거야
Contact me if there is anything
무슨 일 있으면 연락해
This is milk tea
이건 밀크티
I don't drink milk
나는 우유를 마시지 않는다
Let's go
갑시다
Thank you
감사합니다
Thanks
감사해요
thank you thank you
감사합니다 감사합니다
Why are you here
당신은 왜 여기에 있습니까?
Lao Huang
라오 황
why do not you care about me
왜 나한테 관심이 없어?
Absolutely
전적으로
Look what this is
이게 뭔지 봐
What is this?
이게 뭔가요?
I really got into it
나 진짜 푹 빠졌어
Didn't I tell you?
내가 말하지 않았나요?
I can go in without you
너 없이도 들어갈 수 있어
In the future
미래에
We are colleagues
우리는 동료입니다
please
제발
From the personnel department
인사부 출신
What are they doing
그들은 무엇을 하고 있나요?
Even someone like you
너 같은 사람이라도
You can hire
당신은 고용할 수 있습니다
Anyway me too
아무튼 나도
I graduated from an important university
나는 중요한 대학을 졸업했다
in spite of
에도 불구하고
He has no work experience
그 사람은 직장 경험이 없어요.
But I have used the charm of personality
하지만 성격의 매력을 이용했어요
for compensation
보상을 위해
Are you really planning?
정말 계획하고 있나요?
To work with me
나와 함께 일하려면
Maybe you'll get it
어쩌면 당신은 그것을 얻을 것입니다
In the future
미래에
Stop it
그만해요
do not bother me
귀찮게하지 않습니다
I tell you
나는 당신에게 말한다
I will return in a few years
몇년 뒤에 돌아올게요
Don't put me in danger
나를 위험에 빠뜨리지 마세요
Concept?
개념?
and, most importantly
그리고 가장 중요한 것은
Don't let them know
그들에게 알리지 마세요
Our relationship
우리의 관계
Did you understand
당신이 이해 한
Lao Huang
라오 황
Why do I work here?
내가 여기서 일하는 이유는 무엇입니까?
As if I were a thief
마치 내가 도둑이라도 된 것처럼
And also
그리고 또한
Don't play games at work
직장에서 게임을 하지 마세요
no
아니요
What is this?
이게 뭔가요?
it is good
그것은 좋다
Huang Zicheng
황쯔쳉
You have joined the animal group
동물그룹에 가입하셨습니다
I make good use of it
잘 활용하고 있어요
It is the most important screw
가장 중요한 나사입니다
Next to Huang Jaming
황자밍 옆
But I'm not sure
하지만 잘 모르겠어요
Is it
그렇습니까?
Under our control?
우리 통제하에 있나요?
What do you mean?
무슨 뜻이에요?
When the other party started
상대방이 시작했을 때
Huang Zicheng appeared at the crime scene
황쯔청(Huang Zicheng)이 범죄 현장에 나타났다
Although Yao Yao said
야오야오가 말했지만
That Fang Lu called her
Fang Lu가 그녀에게 전화한 것
But I am not reassured
하지만 안심할 수는 없어
I always think
나는 항상 생각한다
That Huang Zicheng is doing a small job
황자성(Huang Zicheng)이 작은 일을 하고 있다고
Are you worried about Yao Yao too
야오야오도 걱정되시나요?
I think it is necessary to make sure
확실히 하는 것이 필요하다고 생각합니다
So as soon as possible
그러니 최대한 빨리
Arrange the task for them
그들을 위해 작업을 준비
Make sure you are concerned
걱정되시는지 확인해보세요
Good
좋은
Director Chu will go to Thailand on Sunday
추 감독은 일요일에 태국으로 갈 예정이다.
To promote
홍보
To develop business abroad
해외사업을 발전시키려면
On a business trip with Director Chu
추 이사님과 출장 중
I can
저 할 수 있어요
Yao Yao what about you
야오야오 넌 어때?
I have a lot
내가 많이
I haven't finished working
나 아직 일 안끝났어
I'm not going
나는 가지 않을 것이다
are you sure?
확실합니까?
Good
좋은
my brother
내 동생
I think there is a hole in this mission
이번 미션에 구멍이 있는 것 같아요
Any hole
어떤 구멍이라도
how did you know
어떻게 알았어?
How did people know about night fog?
사람들은 밤안개를 어떻게 알았나요?
And also
그리고 또한
they asked me
그들은 나에게 물었다
Monitoring report
모니터링 보고서
On Lao Huang's computer
Lao Huang의 컴퓨터에서
This information
이 정보
How do they know that?
그들은 그것을 어떻게 알 수 있습니까?
How important
얼마나 중요한지
How important is this?
이것이 얼마나 중요합니까?
I almost understood
나는 거의 이해했다
that it
그것은 그
We searched for human genes
우리는 인간의 유전자를 검색했습니다
Regarding animal safety
동물 안전에 관해서
Although it is just a monitoring report
비록 모니터링 보고서일 뿐이지만
But it can't
하지만 그럴 수는 없어
To leak it out
그걸 유출시키려고
Your analysis is good
분석이 좋네요
It worked for you so quickly
너무 빨리 효과가 있었어
I want to test you
당신을 시험하고 싶어요
What should I do?
어떻게 해야 하나요?
Do as planned
계획대로 하세요
During your operation
수술 중
Watch some people who are watching you
당신을 지켜보고 있는 몇몇 사람들을 지켜보세요
to remember
기억하다
I will help you check it later
나중에 확인 도와드릴게요
Understood
이해했다
in addition to
게다가
There is another possibility
또 다른 가능성이 있다
what can be
무엇이 될 수 있는가?
A spy is watching you
스파이가 당신을 지켜보고 있다
Some internal equipment
일부 내부 장비
For example computer
예를 들어 컴퓨터
Paper crushing machine
종이 분쇄기
Transmitter
송신기
So you should take advantage
그러니 이점을 활용해야 합니다
this process
이 과정
Go to your uncle's office
삼촌 사무실로 가세요
Inspect all electronic equipment
모든 전자 장비를 검사하세요.
All electronic equipment
모든 전자 장비
Make sure you are safe
안전한지 확인하세요
Well understood
잘 이해했습니다
Don't worry
괜찮아요
This is not a game
이것은 게임이 아니다
No chance of returning
돌아올 가능성은 없습니다
There is only one life
인생은 하나뿐이다
I understood the disorder patient
나는 장애 환자를 이해했다
Did Yao Yao participate in the operation as well
야오야오도 작전에 참여했나
It seems she received
그녀가 받은 것 같아
Mission announcement
미션 발표
Wait for my orders
내 명령을 기다려라
Did you also receive the assignment?
당신도 임무를 받았나요?
What will you do?
당신은 무엇을 할 것인가?
Eat first
먼저 먹어라
Let's talk after you're satisfied
만족한 후에 이야기하자
Why do you look?
왜 보이나요?
I'm not worried at all
전혀 걱정하지 않아요
There's no point in worrying
걱정해도 소용없어
now
지금
At least better than in Macau
적어도 마카오보다는 낫지
No one is forcing us to use a gun
누구도 우리에게 총을 사용하라고 강요하지 않아요
This restaurant is very good
이 레스토랑은 아주 맛있어요
Don't be shy to evaluate online
온라인으로 평가하는 것을 부끄러워하지 마세요
Have you ever thought
생각해 본 적 있니
good idea
좋은 생각
Why are you laughing?
왜 웃어요?
Tell me quickly
빨리 말해줘
Don't get excited
흥분하지 마세요
like before
예전처럼
I play games
나는 게임을 한다
Complete the game mission
게임 미션을 완료하세요
Is this the same thing?
이것도 같은 건가요?
This is real theft
이건 진짜 도둑질이다
Why did you dare to play before?
왜 전에는 감히 놀았나요?
Because you know it's fake
왜냐하면 당신은 그것이 가짜라는 것을 알고 있기 때문입니다.
It's the same thing now
지금도 마찬가지야
Stealing it is against the law
그것을 훔치는 것은 법에 위배됩니다
This is not against the law
이는 법률에 위배되지 않습니다.
do you mean
무슨 뜻인가요?
To make fake
가짜로 만들려면
Of course you can't give them real
물론 당신은 그들에게 진짜를 줄 수는 없습니다
This is not worse
이게 더 나쁘지는 않은데
So what are we going to leak then?
그러면 우리는 무엇을 유출하게 될까요?
We just make one
우리는 하나만 만들어요
Isn't that all?
그게 다 아닌가요?
That's logical
그건 논리적이야
Why do I feel?
내가 느끼는 이유는 무엇입니까?
You are smarter than me
당신은 나보다 똑똑하다
at this time
이 시간에
No kidding
농담하지마
As we expected at first
처음에는 예상했던 대로
There is a nail inside the animal set
동물세트 안에 못이 들어있어요
While executing the task
작업을 실행하는 동안
probably
아마
He will be monitored
그는 감시를 받을 것이다
Verify whether he is a spy or not
그 사람이 스파이인지 아닌지 확인해보세요
So Huang Zicheng
소황자성
The task must be completed
임무가 완료되어야 한다
To get the file
파일을 얻으려면
If in this process
만약 이 과정에서
Screw can be found
나사를 찾을 수 있습니다
This is the best result
이것이 최고의 결과입니다
I will go
나는 갈 것이다
Greeting the group
단체 인사하기
Good
좋은
choose one
하나를 선택하세요
Easy to leak
누출되기 쉬움
What if Mr. Zhang sends
장 씨가 보내면 어떻게 되나요?
To watch us
우리를 지켜보기 위해
if
만약에
Watching us
우리를 지켜보며
We didn't steal
우리는 훔치지 않았어요
not listening
듣지 않는다
So
그래서
We should
우리는해야한다
To steal everything
모든 것을 훔치려고
And forge a copy of it
그리고 그 사본을 위조하세요.
Isn't that all?
그게 다 아닌가요?
forged
서서히 나아가는
no
아니요
I'm still worried
난 아직도 걱정돼
to think
생각하다
I took a risk
나는 위험을 감수했다
Big risk
큰 위험
And they noticed that
그리고 그들은 그것을 알아차렸습니다.
If we fake it
우리가 가짜라면
He created us
그분은 우리를 창조하셨습니다
What will we do if we find out?
우리가 알게 되면 어떻게 할 건가요?
We can't help it
우리는 그것을 도울 수 없다
Let's go and see
가서 보자
Think of a way to stop them
그들을 막을 방법을 생각해 보세요
when
언제
When will you finish
언제 끝낼 거야?
So
그래서
The most important thing now
지금 가장 중요한 건
He finds out who Mr. Zhang is
그는 장씨가 누구인지 알아낸다
This is the only paper
이것이 유일한 종이다
In the future
미래에
I think Mr. Zhang
내 생각엔 장 씨가
Like a shadow
그림자처럼
He kept hiding in the dark
그는 계속 어둠 속에 숨어 있었어
Don't think like that
그렇게 생각하지 마세요
It's not scary
무섭지 않아
correct
옳은
There is no point in thinking too much
너무 많이 생각하는 것은 의미가 없습니다
Let's go
갑시다
Today we have wine
오늘은 와인이 있어요
Today I got drunk
오늘은 술에 취해버렸어
This is correct
이것이 맞습니다
Kelli
켈리
Yaw yaw
요요
If you encounter any danger in the future
앞으로 어떤 위험에 직면하게 된다면
You must protect yourself
당신은 자신을 보호해야합니다
do not care about me
나에 대해 신경 쓰지 마세요
I said that
나는 그렇게 말했다
180 times
180회
I'm tired of hearing
듣기 지겹다
Understood
이해했다
Don't worry
괜찮아요
I won't care about you
나는 당신에 대해 신경 쓰지 않을 것입니다
Maybe he's checking
어쩌면 그 사람이 확인하고 있을지도 모르지
We can't follow it anymore
우리는 더 이상 따라갈 수 없습니다
science
과학
Stop following him
그 사람 팔로우를 중단하세요.
He noticed that
그는 그것을 알아 차렸다
science
과학
Look
바라보다
Mr. Chen
첸 씨
how's it going
어떻게되고 있습니까
According to
에 따르면
Provided by Wu Xi
우시 제공
And monitor the vehicle review
그리고 차량 리뷰를 모니터링하세요
Xiao Yi and the suspect found the target
샤오이와 피의자는 표적을 찾았다
Car riding mode
자동차 라이딩 모드
Up to
까지
more than 90%
90% 이상
This is correct
이것이 맞습니다
Yes
예
Basically can be confirmed
기본적으로 확인 가능
it is him
그 사람이야
We distributed three tracking kits today
오늘 추적 키트 3개를 배포했습니다.
I discovered that his ability to track him
나는 그를 추적하는 그의 능력을 발견했다
Very strong
매우 강한
Checked several times
여러번 확인함
In order not to disturb him
그 사람을 방해하지 않으려면
We give up following him
우리는 그를 따르는 것을 포기합니다
I did well.
나는 잘했다.
He is a professional spy
그는 전문 스파이이다
Professional spy
전문 스파이
You have to be very careful with him
너는 그 사람을 매우 조심해야 해
Open this place
이 장소를 열어보세요
Actually we are now
사실 우리는 지금
at present
현재
Our knowledge of Xiao Yi
Xiao Yi에 대한 우리의 지식
Very limited
매우 제한적
In previous cases
이전의 경우
Xiao Yi appeared
샤오이 등장
It is definitely a spy organization
분명 간첩조직이다
An important member of Tianhai
천해의 중요한 구성원
Let's find out his condition first
먼저 그의 상태를 알아보자
Yes
예
Where does he live? Contact whom
그 사람은 어디에 살고 있나요? 누구에게 연락하세요?
He might find a big fish through it
그는 그것을 통해 큰 물고기를 찾을 수도 있습니다
in addition to
게다가
He has the ability to fight investigation
그는 수사에 맞서 싸울 능력이 있습니다
He has a different opponent
그에겐 상대가 따로 있다
Who we met
우리가 만난 사람
This is a test for us
이것은 우리를 위한 시험이다
be
BE
Keep going to the club
계속 클럽에 가세요
I suddenly disappeared
갑자기 사라졌어요
It might make him suspicious
그 사람을 의심하게 만들 수도 있어
The task you are following
당신이 수행하는 작업
It would be better to be under Tianyang's leadership
Tianyang의 리더십을받는 것이 더 나을 것입니다.
No problem
괜찮아요
if
만약에
He was a motorcycle driver before
그 사람은 예전에 오토바이 운전사였어.
Maybe I've seen you before
어쩌면 난 당신을 전에 본 적이 있을 수도 있어요
Don't worry
괜찮아요
I won't meet him directly
그 사람을 직접 만나지는 않을 거예요
I stress again
또 스트레스 받네
They must be followed secretly
비밀리에 따라야 합니다
I'd rather not follow him
난 그 사람을 따르지 않는 게 좋을 것 같아
It cannot be detected
감지할 수 없습니다.
Good
좋은
Understood
이해했다